

## SISHANKI KASHYAP

### **Content Writer**

### **About Me**

Hello everyone, Sishanki Kashyap is on this side for you guys to check out if you want some fresh content. Writing has been my hobby lately, but now it has become my full-time delight. I want to grow in this field and get immersed more. Catch me out for some determined workpieces.

### **My Contact**

- sishankikashyap@gmail.com
- **(** +91 7063111307
- B-158, Gamma-1, Greater Noida
  -201308
- in www.linkedin.com/in/sishankikashyap

#### **Skills**

- English Proficiency
- Written Communication
- Communication
- Leadership
- Team Communication

## **Education Background**

08/2018- 05/2021 Bachelor of Arts 09/2021-Current - Masters in Arts 04/2010-09/2013- Diploma in Fine Arts

### Language known

- ENGLISH Advance
- HINDI Advance
- ASSAMESE Advance
- BENGALI Upper Intermediet
- NEPALI Intermediet

### **Professional Experience**

## Sarkari School I Content writer, Intern 03/2021-04/2021

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Worked with teams of designers, editors and marketers to create content for client campaigns.
- Developed content for a variety of topics, ranging from technical to lifestyle, for multiple websites.
- Formatted content to adhere to industry-specific style quides.
- Studied and commented on current news and trends.

# United Being Foundation I Content Writer, Intern 05/2021-06/2021

#### Key responsibilities:

- Developed and pitched story ideas to editors.
- Researched and wrote news stories, articles and reviews for online publications.
- Worked with teams of designers, editors and marketers to create content for client campaigns.

## Webmedy- Ardinia Pvt.Ltd | Freelance Content writer 02/2023-04/2023

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Submit work to editors for input and approval
- Update website content as needed
- Write clear marketing copy to promote our products/services